So you really don't want to tell them you're leaving? Are you sure about that?
Yes. With the training those two are going through right now, every last moment counts.
Tell them we'll meet again.
Yeah.
So long.
Goodbye, Leorio.
Hey, hold on a second.
Keep an eye on him for me, will ya?
He acts calm, but he can be reckless.
He's smart, but he doesn't always think things through.
I see he opens up to you more than most people. Do you think you can keep him in check?
Sure. You're very soothing, you know.
Of all the heartbeats in this city, yours is the most pleasant.
It's uplifting, incredibly gentle, and very warm, too.
I think you'd make an excellent teacher, or maybe even a doctor.
I would recommend a career change.
I might have to give it some thought.
Time for me to get serious and hit the books.
I think it's alright.
Thanks.
I think it's katie.
I am low when I grow down,
I appear to stand my turn of Heaven,
I make you turn on my path.
You ain't one but alone
You can fly away.
The world is your shining.
The sun is shining.
You will shine.
The moon is shining.
We'll see you next time.
Number 16 wins Green Island for $27.8 billion!
Thank you very much!
That bastard's out to get every single copy, and he knows exactly what my budget is!
There's only one copy left, and it's gonna be mine, damn it!
What? He left?
He'll be back. He said to keep training hard.
Aw, he didn't have to worry about that.
Wait a minute, I could have sworn that you were happy Kurapika was leaving York New City.
Well, sure I was happy. I just wanted to say bye.
Here. For you from Zepile. He said you'll see him again.
Huh? Mr. Zepile too?
Yeah, and he recovered your hundred million jenny, just like he said he would.
He really did.
Now you can buy your hunter's license back from the pawn shop.
Yeah. Mr. Zepile's awesome! I mean really awesome!
Man, that hunter's license sure is incredible.
The pawn shop forked over a hundred million on the spot.
Probably could have added a couple more zeros if it was sold at auction.
Hey, I know! I should become a professional hunter so I can sell my license!
And forget all about debt! I could live off the interest alone, easy!
All right, let's get cracking! There's no time to waste!
I gotta start prepping for the hunter exam!
Number 16 wins Greed Island for $60.2 billion!
Thank you very much!
$60.2 billion?
That's unheard of!
And to think he managed to win all seven copies up for auction!
I know, I know! But it cost him half his fortune!
An unknown party stole a copy of Greed Island won by Mr. Batera for $30.5 billion.
Not to be discouraged, he won copies for $27.8 billion yesterday and won for $60.2 billion today.
Hmph! There must be some reason he went so far for a video game.
I hear if you beat it, that you receive an actual treasure map at the very end.
Or that a giant dragon appears and offers to grant you a wish.
There are all kinds of rumors out there.
Thank you!
I'm going home.
Earlier today, Mr. Batera won all the copies of Greed Island.
But he's also seeking players to play the game.
Today's the deadline.
There's already an amazing line outside the venue!
I apologize for the long wait, everyone.
We will now begin selecting the players.
And as you're already aware, you must be capable of using Nen in order to play.
The test will proceed as follows.
First, we will need each applicant to demonstrate their Nen.
Once the demonstration phase is complete, we will make our decision.
The judge will be none other than professional hunter, Mr. Tezgera!
The jackpot hunter Tezgera?
Wow!
If he's involved, this game must pay huge dividends!
Alright, we will now begin the test.
Come up one at a time and show me your Ren.
A curtain will block any view of the stage, so the other applicants can't see what's happening.
The test will be over, as soon as we've chosen all 32 of our players.
To participate, step this way and form a line!
That's all they're telling us?
Would the first applicant please step in?
That explanation was so vague, we don't know anything.
But the others are stepping up like it's the only natural response.
They must know.
It's pretty obvious those guys aren't gonna answer any questions.
Our task is simple.
Deduce all we can from the information provided.
Then try our best.
So they're judging us on the entire process.
They've gotta be.
There are about 200 people in the hall.
Around 100 have already lined up.
And at least 50 are still watching closely from the sidelines.
And 20 who haven't moved an inch.
Which group made the right choice?
Next up please.
Next!
Hold on.
Ten people have gone in.
But nobody has come back out again.
Does that mean everyone who went in passed?
This is bad.
Should we get in line?
Those guys are hopeless.
They don't stand a chance of getting in.
I'm talking about the ones still in line.
And those who are waiting nearby.
But the ones who are hovering next to the line are really hopeless.
They're probably waiting around for someone to return so they can ask them what's waiting inside.
If only they'd done a little bit of research.
Or just thought for a second.
Then maybe they'd see there's no point in rushing to the front.
In other words, it's impossible to send in new players.
That's why I'm so careful selecting players.
I get it now.
They're not choosing 32 players this time, are they?
No, they are not.
It's been over 10 years and not a single player has cleared the game.
And as you know, new players can't start Greed Island as long as the old ones are still alive.
So of course, what that really means is they have to save a few spots just in case any extraordinary players pop up and want to join in on the action.
And if I had to hazard a guess, they'll only add about 20 or so in this round.
Personally, I'd say that the ones in line or the ones standing nearby have no shot whatsoever.
Anybody worthwhile either stood up and got in line just as soon as possible, or figured out the trick and stayed in their seats to focus like we did.
Wouldn't you agree, kid?
Gon, you figured out what was going on?
Well, yeah, but it was only a hunch.
I just thought it was only natural.
They want to test everybody who's here, don't they?
And if that's the case, what does it matter if we get in line or not?
Very true.
You win, kid.
Nice thinking.
Yeah, that's pretty impressive.
Not many people can commit to their own logic like you just did.
Nope, not many people at all.
The steeper and more dangerous the path, the better it is to turn half your brain off or you'll never be able to take the plunge.
All right then. Next, please.
The name's Puhat, by the way.
Well, nice to meet you.
The people who act like they're smart are the ones that usually fail.
You know we can hear you.
Still, he's telling the truth.
I was too focused on logically making the right move.
I'm going ahead.
Right. Good luck.
If I'm not willing to take chances, I'll never advance.
Listen, never take risks.
Only act when success is 100% guaranteed.
Otherwise, wait.
Waiting is our most crucial job.
If victory isn't assured, revealing your strength is the most foolish move you can make.
That's my old man's logic.
But I'm not an assassin.
I'm a hunter.
All right, kid. Now let me see your Ren.
Hatsu okay?
That'll be fine.
You can show me anything that properly demonstrates your power.
Prove to me that you can do better than the Ren I saw earlier.
All right then.
Here goes.
He changed his aura into electricity.
It's possible in theory, of course.
But the fact that he learned it from scratch in only four days is unbelievable.
Well, do you need to see any more?
No, you've passed.
That's enough.
But this technique couldn't have fully developed over nights.
You would have to be exposed to enormous amounts of electricity.
It would take years.
Who are you?
Electricity's nothing.
Been shocked since I was born.
Family circumstances, you see.
Seven people.
That guy was right.
The people who passed were the ones who got up immediately,
or the ones who waited in their seats.
Well, I hope Gon's doing okay.
Okay.
Goon!
Killua!
That's awesome!
You got chosen, huh?
Of course I did.
That big sound was you, wasn't it?
Yup!
Honestly.
Those two kids are really something else.
Allow me to be the first to congratulate you.
The 21 people still here have earned the right to play Greed Island.
You will receive 50 billion jenny upon clearing the game.
All the details are there in the contract,
so be sure to read it thoroughly,
and sign it before you leave here at 5 p.m.
Cheers!
Congrats on making it past stage one!
Could you look at this for us?
What?
Contract, huh?
It can be summed up in three points.
First, you can't file any claims if you're injured or you die.
Second, any items you bring out of the game belong to Mr. Batera.
Third, if you clear the game, you receive a 50 billion jenny reward.
I don't see any problems.
Good!
Just sign it and you're all set.
Point two seems important.
It talks about any item that you might bring out of the game.
He's offering an enormous reward, and that's why.
Yeah, but what kind of items?
I don't care.
Because I'm not playing for items.
I just want to get as close as possible to Gene.
Well, see ya.
Good luck on your exam, Leorio.
Thanks.
You two be careful, okay?
You'll be a doctor next time we see you.
Wait, does that mean we won't see each other for at least four years?
We're going to clear that game fast.
It isn't going to take that long.
Then I'll be ready.
Hmm.
Good luck.
Pretty-hmm.
Oof.
Good luck.
You guys are together.
You're surrounded by the group.
Come.
Good luck.
You're a little palm.
You're welcome.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Now then, I'll just explain a few things before we begin.
The individual game copies are not independent of each other.
No matter which console you start from, you'll all arrive at the same place.
Think of it as a virtual area, accessible from any spot on this planet.
I'll hand out memory cards to each of you.
Once I do, head straight into the game.
But first, we'll decide the order.
Order?
The game only allows one player at a time to enter into it.
We'll decide now to avoid any bickering inside the game.
Fine. Then how about rock, paper, scissors?
Yes! I'm first!
Hold on. Aren't you the one who's already obtained a save file?
Oh, damn it. I'm number 17.
Would you like to use it?
Don't worry. Your initial destination is always the same, regardless of your save file.
Gene.
This game is a message from him to me.
I'm gonna trust him.
I'm gonna go for it. I'll use my own card.
Okay. Then put the ring on, and whenever you're ready to go, begin.
Go.
Wait for me in the starting area, okay?
Hmph.
The next person can go as soon as the screen says, now playing.
Welcome to Greed Island, sir. You must be go'n freaks.
I will explain how the game works. Would that interest you?
Sure.
In this game, anyone who is wearing a ring has two spells available to them.
They are called Book and Gain.
Place the hand wearing the ring in front of you, and say Book.
Uh, Book!
You see, your task is to seek out and collect certain cards.
That binder is for storing all of the cards you've collected.
Now please take a look at the first page.
Each slot is labeled with a number.
With these, you can only place a card if its number corresponds with the one on the slot.
These are your specified slots.
Please flip ahead a few pages.
Wait, these aren't numbered.
That's right.
With these slots, you can place any card you choose.
These are called your free slots.
Specified slots are numbered 0 to 99, making 100.
Then, you have another 45 free slots.
To clear the game, you must fill the 100 specified slots.
Then, and only then, will you be successful.
So I just need to collect 100 cards, huh?
Correct.
More specifically, you must obtain 100 items, and after transforming them, put them in your binder.
Transform?
That's correct.
If you obtain a sword, for example, it will instantly transform into a card.
If you wish to use a card as the item, you must first use the spell Gain.
I get it.
However, once you've returned a card to item form, you can never transform it into a card again.
If you want the card version of the item, you must once again acquire it.
Make sense so far?
Uh, I think so.
Now, there are two other cases where an item can't become a card.
In the first of those two cases, you reach the item's maximum conversion limit.
Wait, card conversion limit?
Yes.
Every item in this game has a limit to the number of times it can be converted.
For instance, if an item has a conversion limit of three, and there are three other players who have converted that item into a card already, then that's it.
The fourth player who obtains said item cannot change it into a card.
In the second case, a card will turn back into an item unless it's in your book within one minute.
In this case, it is also irreversible.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Yeah, kinda.
Finally, the most important word of caution.
My brain is getting full.
In this game, whenever a player dies, both their binder and their ring are destroyed.
And the contents will cease to exist.
I don't think that would matter much to a dead person.
That concludes my explanation.
You will need to learn about all of the other aspects of the game by playing it for yourself.
Right. I understand. And thanks a lot.
I wish you the very best of luck on your journey.
Now please walk down the stairs.
Loading all saved data, I have a message for you from Mr. Gene Freaks.
Gene!
Glad to see you made it in, Gon.
This is the game I made with my friends.
Hope you like it.
If you thought there'd be a clue to help you find me, though, well, too bad.
I just wanted to show off our game.
It doesn't matter what brought you here, because you won't be able to leave until you obtain a specific item.
So go ahead.
Play your heart out.
Gohan has finally stepped foot inside the legendary game, Greed Island.
A new adventure is about to begin.
Good luck.
いつむ!
IBTI otros 40000
Mike
Arrھی
lado
Y
hier
y
der
wat
Coming up, the Great Island Tutorial!